gokunming.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy policy - GoKunming

_(Last updated March 19, 2013)_

## Registration Information

Registration is required to access some features of the GoKunming platform (such as posting in the Forums section). The registration process asks for a unique and valid email address as well as some demographic information. GoKunming will not share, distribute or sell this information with any other person or entity. This includes mail servers, other site users and even your mom.

## User Generated Content and other Public Activities

We offer our users opportunities to engage in public activities on GoKunming. "Public activities" are any actions you take on the website that are designed to be visible to other users — including comments, forum posts, business ratings or any other items that you submit.

Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name, ID or avatar becomes public and may be used by GoKunming for promotional materials. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.

We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in classified ads, comments, forums or reviews. GoKunming has no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or any of your submissions that are a result of your public activities.

GoKunming highly recommends its users not publish their phone numbers or email addresses in public places. If you deem it entirely necessary, please use the following format to avoid data collection by robots: yourname[at]example[dot]com.

If a user decides to cancel their GoKunming account we will be happy to deactivate it for them contingent upon them providing verification of their account ownership. Account deactivation does not neccesarily remove all of the user's public activity on the site. This is in order to maintain the continuity of forum threads, listing reviews and conversations in article comment sections.

## Device Information

We may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access GoKunming, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language and other transactional information.

## Non-personal Data Collection

GoKunming logs Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our web site and mobile applications.
